- Terrific.
- It has more food too.
All right. Come on, come on.
RAJESH [SINGING]:
I'm coming up
(Raj(leaving, singing):)So you better get this party started
(Raj(leaving, singing):)I'm coming up
I'm coming up, yeah
So you better get this party started
- Hey.
- Hey, good news.
(Howard:)You don't have to sulk
about Penny anymore.
(Howard:)There are hundreds of Croatian women
just waiting for you to contact them.
"Anything-for-a-Green-Card.com"?
I'll lend you my username.
It's Wealthy Big Penis.
- You're joking.
- You gotta make it easy for them.
(Howard:)They're just learning English.
(Leonard:)Pass.
You're just gonna
sit around here and mope...
...while Penny is out with Dr. Apu
from the Kwik-E-Mart?
(Leonard:)It's not a date and that's racist.
(Howard:)It can't be racist.
He's a beloved character on The Simpsons.
(Leonard:)Let's just eat so I can get to bed.